

## Contact

agmanpurohit@gmail.com

Ahmedabad

+91 63750 26232

# Skills

HTML5

CSS3

Figma

JavaScrip ES6+ (Basic)

Responsive Design

ReactJS Framework (Basic)

CSS Preprocessors (Sass)

Problem-solving

Eagerness to learn

# Languages

English 50%

Hindi 100%

Gujarati 90%

# Agman Rajpurohit

## About me

I'm Agman Rajpurohit, a driven BCA graduate currently thriving as a Process Associate at Diya Infotech. My analytical mind and relentless curiosity fuel my passion for web research, allowing me to navigate the digital landscape with precision and efficiency.

# **Experience**

#### **Process Associate**

Diya Infotech 2023 - Present

Collect data and company information through online findings, Consolidate information into the workflow system

#### **Cyber Security Analyst - Internship**

Pristine InfoSolution Pvt Ltd, Ahmedabad Feb 2022 - Jul 2022 worked as a Trainer and took sessions for students on Ethical Hacking and cyber security topics.

## Education

## (2023) Certification in Full Stack Development

Grras Solutions Pvt. Ltd, Ahmedabad

I gained knowledge about JavaScript, HTML, CSS, ReactJS, and MongoDB.

# (2021-2022) Certified Information Tech and Penetration Testing

Pristine InfoSolution Pvt Ltd, Ahmedabad

I gained understanding of ethical hacking and web application testing.

### (2017-2020) Bechelor of Computer Application

Jai Narayana Vyas University, Jodhpur